agilealliance.org 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Agile Alliance

Effective: May 25, 2018

## Introduction

Agile Alliance ( **“Organization”** or **“We”** ) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.agilealliance.org (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or
  * any third party (including our [affiliates](http://www.agilealliance.org/the-alliance#affiliates)), including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.

If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy.

This policy may change from time to time. When we make changes to the policy, you will be asked to accept the policy with it’s changes the next time you log in to the Website.

## Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use.

If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.

If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@agilealliance.org.

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, biography, and social media profiles (“personal information”);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as country, company, and title; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our affiliates and service providers.

### Information You Provide to Us

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of subscribing to our website, purchasing a membership or posting information. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”).

Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

### Usage Details, IP Addresses And Cookies

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.

### Use of Intercom Services

We use third-party analytics services to help understand your usage of our services. In particular, we provide a limited amount of your information (such as your email address and sign-up date) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product.

Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship so that we can improve our service to you. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s).

As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit[ https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy). Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at[ https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms). If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please [contact us](https://www.agilealliance.org/contact-us).

## How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your membership, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To register you for events and provide you information about those events.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * To connect you with an event sponsor when you agree to have your badge scanned during an event.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

## How Long We Keep Your Information

We store your information for as long as you maintain your membership, or for two years after your last login, whichever period is longer.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Agile Alliance’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Agile Alliance about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Agile Alliance, our members, event attendees or others.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

### Tracking Technologies and Advertising.

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

### Promotional Offers from Agile Alliance.

We do not directly provide your personal information to third parties for the purpose of promoting their products or services. We may periodically send you promotions about our own products and services. We may also send you pomotions about third party products and services on their behalf.

If you do not wish to have your email address used by Agile Alliance to promote our own or third parties’ products, services, or events you can opt-out in email messages you receive with such promotions or by sending us an email stating your request to info@agilealliance.org.

If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to Agile Alliance as a result of a membership purchase or event registration.

## Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change the personal information in your profile by logging into the Website and visiting your[ account profile page](https://www.agilealliance.org/membership/edit-profile/).

You can also login and visit the [privacy settings page](https://www.agilealliance.org/membership/edit-profile/) to do any of the following:

  * Download your personal information stored on our site
  * Fix incorrect personal information on our site
  * Ask a question or raise a concern about your personal information on our site
  * Delete your personal information from our site

Please note we cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users.

## Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

## International Transfers

Your data may be transferred to other countries and by using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence. If you are located in the European Union, we may store and share your personal data with companies located outside of the European Economic Area.

We will always do our best to ensure security of your data. We aim to use US-based providers that are part of the EU-US Privacy Shield. You may always request information on how and where your data is processed and stored.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website home page.

The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.

You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you.

## Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, [contact us](mailto:info@agilealliance.org).
